What is the single most important lesson
you've learned about yourself
as a leader?
The goal of this experience
was never just to learn new concepts.
It was to build new habits.
The final step in leading yourself
is to consciously decide which of these new behaviors
you want to hardwire into your leadership identity,
moving from a temporary practice
to a permanent part of your operating system.
After going through this experience,
a manager realized that his habit of drive-by feedback
was causing anxiety.
His new hardwired habit
became scheduling brief intentional feedback sessions.
He put it on his calendar every Friday.
It became a part of his system.
Your play is to look through your playbook,
identify the one new practice
that has been most impactful for you.
Now, schedule a reoccurring block on your calendar
to ensure it continues to stay in practice.
In three months, the newness of this experience
will have worn off.
What is one system or accountability check
you can put into place now
to ensure you don't revert to old leadership habits?
Turn to the hardwire your habits drill in your playbook
to document your commitment
and set your new accountability system.
Now that you've cemented your own habits,
let's focus on celebrating your player success.
I'll see you in the next video.